gorkanajobs.co.uk 2015-12-06

# GorkanaJobs.com | Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**Why do we have a privacy policy?**

Gorkana is committed to privacy for everyone who accesses the site www.gorkana.co.uk ("the Website"). Under the Data Protection Act 1998, we must comply with certain regulations that are designed to ensure that any data you provide to us is processed with due care and attention.

This privacy policy explains the kind of personal data we collect and how it will be used.

More information can be found [here](http://gorkana.com/privacy/):

If you have any questions, comments or suggestions regarding our use of your data, privacy and the Website, or if you wish to withdraw consents you have given (as described below) to any use of your personal information, please contact us at [privacy@gorkana.com](mailto:privacy@gorkana.com) or write to:

Data Protection Officer  
Gorkana Group  
Discovery House  
28-42 Banner Street  
London EC1Y 8QE

**What sort of data do we collect?**  
Gorkana collects personal and professional data from you for use on the Website enabling fellow users of the Website to access information about you, your employer or business. This data consists of information such as your name, place of work, address (which may also be a home address if you provide us with that information), telephone number and e-mail address.

We also collect information in the aggregate to provide us with a better understanding of the users of our website as a group, but which does not contain personally identifiable information. 

The personal information we collect may change from time to time, but will only be collected when you give it voluntarily or if the information is available in the public arena. 

**Why do we process this data?  **

We process this data as necessary to enhance the information available to users and improve accessibility of the Website for yourself and other users. We may also use data collected in the aggregate to help us to understand our users as a group so that we can provide a better service. 

**Consent  **

By using the Website and by registering your details with us, and providing information, articles and alerts to us or direct to the Website you consent to us collecting and processing that data and disclosing on the Website all information and content supplied making it available to prospective contacts and their clients, journalists and other Website users in connection with the operation of the Website. 

**Do we pass data to third parties?  **

Where necessary we may pass data to third parties that help us to process data. We may also share aggregate information with selected third parties but we do not disclose individual names or any identifying information. Your personal information may be transferred to and the Website (which may display your data) may be accessible in countries outside the European Economic Area, which may not have privacy or data protection laws comparable to European law.  
**How is this data safeguarded?  **

The security of your data is extremely important to us. Access to your personal data is only provided to our staff and third parties who help us to process data and, in order to help with the functioning of the Website, prospective customers, and members of the PR, journalist and business community. 

**How do we let you know if our policy changes?**

Any policy changes, either due to business reasons or future changes in legislation, will be posted on the Website and, if substantial, may be promoted through e-mail notification. 

**Updates, new products/services and other related matters  **

We may also use your personal information to inform you of new services, changes to the Website and other related matters which we feel may be of interest to you.  
We may use personal information obtained from you to contact you and send you information regarding similar products or services, but we will always give you the opportunity to refuse any future use of your personal information in this way. 

**Cookies**

We may utilise "cookie" technology to make your use of the Website more convenient and to assist in our efforts to gather and track the information described above. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from the Website. The cookie may be a 'session cookie' or a 'persistent cookie'. A session cookie is automatically deleted once you either turn off your computer or exit from the portion of the Website that placed the session cookie on your computer. A persistent cookie is stored on your computer's hard drive until it expires or is deleted. 

The information collected by cookies may be used to help us improve the Website. It enables us to know who you are when you return to the Website, allowing us to store and access your preferences and customise your experience of the Website. 

If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, you can disable cookies through your Internet browser. If you want to know how to do this, please look at the "Help" menu on your browser. Disabling cookies may prevent you from accessing features of the Website
